Introduction.
Throughout your radiation treatment,
it is very important to eat well
and pay close attention to your nutrition.
Ideally,
this means eating without restrictions
as much of the foods you wish to eat
to sustain a healthy body weight.
Taking in enough nutrition and calories is important
to your body’s ability to bounce back and
heal in between radiation treatments.
Without
appropriate nutrition and caloric intake
harmful effects from radiation
exposure can build up
and your healthy tissues will not recover
as quickly from day to day.
This video will explain common
nutrition challenges during treatment.
Introduce you to your nutrition
support team
and explain ways that we can support
you if you do lose weight.